RALPH MATTHEW C. MAGLAYA

3546 Lubiran St. Bacood, Sta. Mesa, Manila

Email: maglayaralph26@gmail.com

Phone: +639306488574

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/immaglaya26 Portfolio: https://portfoliorap.netlify.app/



SUMMARY

I have developed numerous websites and have remained dedicated to securing new projects. My commitment extends to continually learning about emerging technologies and staying abreast of the latest methods and tools within the industry. I actively seek to tackle real-world challenges, glean insights from experienced individuals, enhance my knowledge, and position myself for a successful career in the programing field.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

2020 to 2024 Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Polytechnic University of the Philippines

San Juan Campus, San Juan City, Metro Manila

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Python, PHP, Javascript, Java, Typescript, C#

Frameworks: Express, Next JS, React JS, Tailwind, Bootstrap, Redux, Spring Boot, Laravel,

Codeigniter

Libraries: Node js, Jwt, Bcrpyt, Hash Mobile Development: Java, Kotlin

Database Management: MySql, Firebase, MongoDb, Sql

Version Control: Git

Cloud Platforms: Microsoft Azure

DevOps: Docker

Other: Postman, Github, Visual Studio Code, Figma, MySql Workbench

AWARDS AND RECOGNITIONS

2023	President's List Award (1st Semester)
2022	President's List Award (2 nd Semester)
2021	Dean's List Award (2 nd Semester)
2021	President's List Award (1st Semester)

SEMINARS ATTENDED	
2023	Back end developer (BPI)
2024	Guardians of the Digital Realm: Navigating Cybersecurity Challenges in the modern age.
2024	System Integration and Security

WORK EXPERIENCES

On the Job Training Programmer (2024 - 2024)

- Develop a website application called Employee Directory System for marketing employees in the Unison Computer System, Inc.
- Conducted the testing of the system in the employee, security of the website.

Freelance Developer (2022 - 2024)

- Develop a website application for the capstone, small business company by using frameworks web dev.
- Integrated payment gateways and implemented user authentication and authorization functionalities.
- Conducted testing and debugging to ensure the website's functionality and responsiveness across different devices.
- Designed and developed mobile app for a startup using Kotlin android studio.
- Troubleshooted and resolved issues related to installation, configuration, and usage of software applications.
- Assist the client for the domain registration, website hosting, and server management tasks.